

CONTACT

0755566810 claudiababan95@yahoo.com Bucharest, Romania

SKILLS

Computer Science

- C#
- C++
- Java
- .NET Framework
- Selenium
- Microsoft SQL Server
- HTML
- CSS
- PHP
- WordPress
- Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Access, Outlook)

Architecture

- Photoshop
- AutoCAD
- Revit
- 3dsMax
- SketchUp

LANGUAGES

English C1 French B1

CLAUDIA BABAN-MIHĂILĂ

I can prove that I will be an asset in a team due to that fact that I have experience in two separate fields, Architecture and IT, offers me the opportunity to have different perspectives – a more creative one and a technical one.

EXPERIENCE

COMPUTER SCIENCE AND ROBOTICS TEACHER

Academia de Robotica, Bucharest | 06.2021-07.2022

My role was to teach children from 3 to 12 years old various subjects like Robotics, general computer information, Scratch, C++.

PMO - PROJECT BASED

Idemia, Bucharest | 06.2021-07.2022

I was hired on a project to help write and review project documentation, the language used being English UK. My role was to cover all the needs of the project in terms of drafting, reviewing, transmission of documents in various formats, such as: Word, Excel, PowerPoint, SharePoint.

BREEAM CONSULTANT

Cundall, Bucharest | 07.2018-03.2019

My role was to check architectural and engineering documentation, in order to determine if the current construction can receive the required points to be BREEAM certified.

EDUCATION

COMPUTER SCIENCE AND BUSINESS MANAGEMENT

Romanian-American University, Bucharest | 2019-2022

Bachelor's Degree

The exam had two stages: written exam (score 9.60/10) and a project (score 10/10). The final score was 9.80/10. The final project consisted of developing a management and performance application destined for educational centers for children. It was developed using C#, .NET Framework and Microsoft SQL Server.

GPA: 9.86

EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

Student Scientific Communications Session

Participated every semester with papers on subjects related to economy and app development.

STRENGHTS

- Ability to Prioritize
- Always on Time
- Best at Delivering Results
- Communicating with People
- Flexible
- Optimist
- Organized
- Problem Solver
- Team Oriented
- Tech-Savvy

ARCHITECTURE

University of Architecture and Urbanism "Ion Mincu", Bucharest | 2014 - 2019

One semester Erasmus scholarship in 2018 in Leuven, Belgium.

CERTIFICATES

LEARN TO CODE WITH HTML, CSS, PHP, JAVASCRIPT

Digital Nation | 2021

CIBERSECURITY ESSENTIALS

Cisco Networking Academy | 2021

GOOGLE ADS SEARCH CERTIFICATION

Google | 2021

DATABASE DESIGN AND PROGRAMMING WITH SQL

Oracle | 2014

CAMBRIDGE ESOL LEVEL 2 CERTIFICATE CAE

Cambridge | 2013

PUBLICATIONS

Guide to cheap, durable and easy-to-implement solutions to increase the comfort level, reduce the energy consumption and increase the home's energy independence

APMCR 2019

http://www.apmcr.org/wp-content/uploads/2017/07/Ghid-desolutii-pentru-locuinte-nZEB.pdf

Subassemblies Catalog Vol. 1 Framework Solutions for Thermal Insulation Systems / Catalog Subansambluri Vol. 1 Solutii cadru pentru sisteme de anvelope termoizolante

UAUIM Bucharest, 2018

ISBN: 978-606-638-178-9

Composite Facade Thermal Insulation Systems "ETICS" / Sisteme Termoizolante Compozite de Fațadă "ETICS"

ETICS, 2017

http://qetics.ro/sisteme-etics/caiet-cu-solutii-cadru/